Water is really a good thing.
Sister Gesang.
You were so badly injured.
Drinking some water will make you feel better.
It doesn't work that fast.
It just restored a little bit of my strength.
Let's hurry to Brother Qingxuan's side.
We don't know the situation there yet.
Okay.
Golden blade shines,
breaking through all obstacles.
Embracing the origin and returning to the center,
heaven and earth shake.
Sister,
when can we ascend to become immortals?
Heaven must be really fun.
As long as we sisters are together,
what does it matter if we become immortals?
Then you must always stay with me.
It's a promise.
Sister.
Wait for my return.
My sister.
There is a Sanshan Liu in heaven.
There,
lives a High God.
Sister,
what are you looking at?
Come back earlier this time.
Wait for me.
You lied to me.
I never expected
that this matter
would drag you into the abyss.
What a pity.
Since you have attained the right path
and become a Golden Immortal,
why did you still disturb her peace?
My sister and I could have lived carefree in the Three Realms.
My sister promised me herself
to guard the Hanmei Dock with me
and watch all the snow in the mortal world.
But you,
you ruined her cultivation path
and our promise.
I will make you pay with your life.
If I didn't help her,
she would have been destroyed by the heavenly lightning.
What?
The heavenly law is strict.
How could we arbitrarily change it?
That day,
she would rather lose all her cultivation
than follow the heavenly rules.
If I didn't agree to help her keep that thread of longing,
the nine-fold lightning would strike,
and her body and soul would be destroyed.
This thread of longing
not only kept her alive
but
also caused her to
fall into a love tribulation.
This action breaks the rules.
How could I not know?
But after a thousand years of hard cultivation
to encounter immortal destiny,
if it fails at the last step
and her body and soul are destroyed,
what's the point of
this righteous path?
So,
you were banished to the mortal realm
all because of my sister?
Although my descent to the mortal realm started with her,
I was not banished.
I came to this mortal world
to do what I want
and meet who I want to see.
But I didn't expect
that she would also give up her immortal status
and come to this mortal world.
What?
My sister is also in this mortal world?
Bai Jingqing
volunteered to descend to the mortal realm.
Why did she have to do this?
Since the High God descended to the mortal realm,
Bai Jingqing
felt that it was because of her thread of longing.
So she resolutely gave up her immortal status
and entered the mortal world.
Where is she now?
Right now,
she is in Tushan.
What?
Where is she?
Master, your immortal power has recovered.
It is indeed him.
The Way of Heaven is unfair.
Why does it toy with us sisters like this?
Sisters?
Who?
When has the Way of Heaven ever been partial?
Every drink and peck,
are predestined.
You are merely in this game,
mistaking opportunities for calamities.
High God.
Although this demon has gone astray,
she has a thousand years of cultivation.
The Li Sword came down to the mortal realm without permission.
The Heavenly Venerable is looking for a sword attendant.
If she is allowed to make up for her mistakes
by guarding this blade for ten thousand years,
would it be possible?
If so,
it would be a win-win solution.
Are you willing to cultivate with me
to make up for your mistakes?
You want to take me in?
Don't think everyone wants to
have anything to do with you immortals.
Hai Hui.
Jie Qianghai.